9apps.com 2019-12-11

# Privacy policy - 9Apps

## UCWeb Privacy policy

Last update: [Effective May 25, 2018]

About Us The information collected by UCWeb Security Use of the information collected Where we store your data Viewing, changing or removing your personal information Controlling over your data Data retention Changes to the Privacy Policy Contacting us and making a complaint

### 1\. About us

UCWeb offers a variety of measures to protect user privacy when they are using UCWeb Services including UCWeb Sites, UCWeb Applications (“apps”), and/or other UCWeb Services.

UCWeb has created this Policy to explain our privacy practices so you will understand what information about you is collected, and how it is used and disclosed.

Any references in this Policy to “UCWeb “, “we”, “our”, “us” etc. will be interpreted as a reference to us. Our contact details, and those of our representative in the EU and of our data protection officer can be found below under “Contacting us and making a complaint”.

### After reading this Privacy Policy you will have learned that:

  * We take security measures to safeguard your information;
  * We use your information to enhance your experience with UCWeb Services, to improve these Services, to make them better, more user-friendly and more relevant; 
  * We will not share your personally identifiable information with third parties other than set out in this Privacy Policy; 
  * We may use non-personally identifiable information to perform relevant services.
  * This Privacy Policy doesn’t apply to:   
The information practices of other companies and organizations that advertise our services   
Services offered by other companies or individuals, including products or sites that may include UCWeb services, be displayed to you in search results, or be linked from our services 

Whether you are new to UCWeb or a long-time user, please do take the time to get to know our practices – and if you have any questions please feel free to contact us. 

### 2\. The information collected by UCWeb

#### Manually provided information

You may provide your personal information to us, such as your username and email addresses, when you access certain Services offered via the UCWeb Application, for instance,when you create an account on UCWeb Services (including login with other third party accounts). It is your choice whether to send this personal information to us.

If you give us feedback or contact us via e-mail, we will collect your name and email address, as well as any other content included in the email, in order to send you a reply. 

When you participate in one of our surveys, we may collect additional information provided by you to us as part of the surveys. You may also provide other types of Information to us voluntarily if you contact us via e-mail requesting support from UCWeb. It is your choice whether to send such personal information to us. 

In addition, when you use UCWeb Services, UCWeb will have access to information you post to UCWeb including, but not limited to, threads and comments you post in forums. 

#### Automatically collected information

To make UCWeb Services more useful to you, we may collect information from you, including but not limited to:

  * Software information, such as version, distribution, system version and application list;
  * Hardware information, such as IMEI, MAC address of your device, model info, manufacturer;
  * Information regarding your usage, such as browser type, language preference, time and time zone, errors and reports, browsing history, buttons clicked, settings, typing in the URL bar; 
  * Network information: IP address, network carrier, rough location according to the IP address or WiFi connected by / around you, referring site, and speed of each visitor request; 
  * Location of your device or computer (if you grant permission).

When you are visiting UCWeb Sites, we also use cookies (and similar technologies) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and what you search and view. Cookies etc. are computer files that are saved to your device and which may store information about you, your device, and your browser and that may be used to transmit that information to us. For example, cookies are used to identify your device and record the visit so that the UCWeb Services can allow you access to your account without requiring you to re-enter the information. 

**When you are visiting UCWeb website: you may choose to delete cookies or other tracking mechanisms on your browser anytime you want through your browser’s settings. You may also choose to have non-essential cookies (and similar technologies) not used by us when you access and use UCWeb Services by amending your settings at –your browser’s settings (if applicable).**

#### Information from other sources

We may obtain information about you from business partners, contractors, and other third parties and add it to our account information or other information we have collected. We may add this information to the information we have already collected from you via UCWeb Services in order to improve UCWeb Services. 

We may allow users to log in with their Facebook or Google log in information. Under these circumstances and if you have given your consent, we may have access to your profile information stored on the Facebook and/or Google applications (as applicable), including name, email address, picture, gender, age-range, birthday, friends list, marital status and employment history, and in addition in relation to Facebook, education history and religion. 

#### Information Accuracy

When you provide personal information to us, you agree to provide accurate information only, and agree that we may assume its accuracy and rely on it. If we provide means for you to update your information, you agree to update the information to keep it accurate. 

### 3\. Security

UCWeb is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of industry-standard security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. UCWeb has strict restrictions on access to user data. Yet, no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while UCWeb uses reasonable efforts to protect your personal information, UCWeb cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

### 4\. Use of the information collected

In general, personal information you submit to us is used either to respond to requests that you make, or to help us serve you better. We use your personal information in the following ways: 

  * for improvement of UCWeb Services management and experience;
  * to provide you more personalized / customized service;
  * for editorial and feedback purposes; for statistical analyses of user preferences;
  * for smarter defense against malicious websites;
  * for smarter auto correction and personal recommendation on URL;
  * for bookmark synchronization and others functions on the cloud;
  * for more convenient change of settings by turning on/off toggles on your phone;
  * for product development and content improvement;
  * to send newsletters, surveys, offers, and other promotional materials related to UCWeb Services and for other marketing purposes (where permitted by law); and 
  * to provide your information to third parties pursuant to legal obligations.

#### Use by UCWeb

UCWeb may use the information on you in the following ways:

  * For the purpose of legitimate interests being pursued by us in relation to the UCWeb Services that we provide. For example, we will use your information to: 
    * to provide our UCWeb Services and features to you, to measure and improve those services and features and to provide you with customer and technical support; 
    * to provide our UCWeb Services and features to you, to measure and improve those services and features and to provide you with customer and technical support; 
    * for statistical purposes and for reporting to allow us, for example, to monitor performance and detect technical problems; 
    * to release aggregated non-personally information such as usage trend; 
    * to enhance and personalise your use of the UCWeb Services based on this information; 
    * to contact you with any service-related announcements from time to time; 
    * to ensure that content from the UCWeb Services are presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer; and 
    * to detect and prevent fraud. 
  * Where it is necessary for the performance of a contract with you.
  * To provide marketing information and surveys to you in relation to the UCWeb Services and to provide you with advertisements concerning our products and services where you have given your consent, or we are otherwise legally entitled to do so and it is in our legitimate interests to provide such information to you; if you do not wish to be contacted in this way, you can contact us using the contact details below or the “unsubscribe” button in communications with you. 
  * In order to comply with any legal obligation that we have, in connection with any legal proceedings, or in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights. 

Where we have relied on our legitimate interests to process your personal data, you may contact us to obtain more information, including in relation to our assessment of the impact on you. 

Where we have relied on consent to process your personal information, you may withdraw your consent at any time by contacting us using the contact details below. 

#### Use by third parties

We do not share your personal information with others except as indicated below, or otherwise agreed by you. 

#### Online Advertisement by Third Party Advertisers

UCWeb Service is connected to certain advertisement platforms including AdMob by Google, Facebook Audience Network, and Intowow (‘Third Party Advertisers’).   
Information including device type and model, network provider, browser type, language, package name, keywords, version, operating system type, time and time zone, device IP address, network connection type and device GPS location (only if you provide permission), and your mobile advertising identifiers, such as your Apple IDFA or Google AAID, will be shared with the Third Party Advertisers.   
To learn more, please refer to their Privacy Policy:   
<https://policies.google.com/privacy>   
<https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation>   
<http://www.intowow.com/privacy/>

#### Login with UC Account

When you choose to login to a third party website / services with UC Account, you agree to share your UC Account information with the third party, including but not limited to your user name, your name, your alias, your profile picture and your contact information. Such third party websites / services are not controlled by us. When you visit such website or services you do so at your own risk. These website or services may have their own privacy policies in place, which we recommend you review. We do not assume any responsibility or liability for such website or services, the content of such website or services and their privacy practices, nor do we endorse them. We encourage you to familiarize yourself with the privacy statements provided by such website or services prior to providing them with information about you or entering into any transactions on them. 

#### Service providers

We may share your personal information, which may include your name and contact information (including email address) with third parties that perform certain services on our behalf. These services may include providing support, performing data analysis, and providing and supporting Site functionality and features. To the extent we provide access to your personal information to a service provider, they are not permitted to share or use the information for any purpose other than providing services to us. 

#### Other situations

We also may disclose your personal information:

  * In response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us. We reserve the right, but do not undertake a duty, to notify you of court orders, subpoenas or other legal process if allowed. If you do not want us to respond to legal process compelling us to disclose your information, you need to obtain a valid order permitting us to refuse to disclose it and serve the order on us at least 3 business days before the response deadline. 
  * When we believe disclosure is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement; or to enforce the Site terms and conditions or other agreements or policies. 
  * In connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business, a divestiture, merger, consolidation, reorganization, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy, including to prospective or actual purchasers in connection with any of these transactions. 
  * We may share aggregated, non-personally identifiable information publicly and with our partners – like publishers, advertisers or connected sites. For example, we may share information publicly to show trends about the general use of our services. 

### 5\. Where we store your data

We maintain servers around the world, the data that we collect from you may be transferred to and stored at, a destination outside of the country where you live. It may also be processed by staff who work for us or one of our suppliers. 

**By using the UCWeb Services, you consent to your personal data being transferred outside of the country where you live.**

### 6\. Viewing, changing or removing your personal information

You can view the personal information from the account you created and change them as you like. When changing or updating your personal information, we may ask you to verify your identity first. Please note that we may be required by law to store the information we collect, even after you have terminated your use of the UCWeb Services. 

For technical reasons, it may be impossible for us to determine whether you have stopped using the UCWeb Services. For mobile applications, it may also be impossible for UCWeb to determine whether you have deleted the application. In such cases, we reserve the right to remove your account and the information you have provided to us if you have not used the Services for an extended period of time. 

### 7\. Controlling over your data

If you have used UCWeb Services within the EEA, we provide you an opportunity to manage your information, you can learn more in our [[information management guide]](https://web.archive.org/about/privacy_policy_guide.html)

### 8\. Data retention

We only keep your information for as long as is reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy and to fulfil our legal obligations. 

When you delete data, we follow an internal deletion policy to make sure that your data is safely and completely removed from our servers or retained only in anonymized form. 

In some cases, rather than provide a way to delete data, we store it for a predetermined period of time. For each type of data, we set retention timeframes based on the reason for its collection. For example, to ensure that our services display properly on many different types of devices, we may retain browser width and height for up to 12 months. 

We will securely erase your information in advance of these deadlines if we decide that we no longer need it. 

### 9\. Application

Our Privacy Policy applies to all of the services offered by UCWeb. 

Our Privacy Policy does not apply to services offered by other companies or individuals, including products or sites that may be displayed to you through the browser, or other sites linked from our services. Our Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of other companies and organizations who advertise our services, and who may use cookies, pixel tags and other technologies to serve and offer relevant ads. 

### 10\. Changes to the Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy will be periodically revised and may be changed with or without notice. The updated Privacy Policy will be posted on the UCWeb sites. By using or continuing to use the Services you agree to review the Privacy Policy periodically such that you are aware of any modifications. If you do not agree to the Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy, you should not use any of the UCWeb Services. 

### 11\. Contacting us and making a complaint

Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [help@idc.ucweb.com](mailto:help@idc.ucweb.com). 

If you are not satisfied with our response or you believe our use of your information does not comply with data protection law, you can make a complaint to the relevant privacy regulator. 

We want to be as transparent as possible about the changes we make to our Privacy Policy. see the previous versions of the policy. We've also included a page that compares the currey version to make it as easy as possible to see what has changed. 

  * Effective July 14, 2014
    * Comparison
